(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
いらっしゃいませ。
Welcome.
火威青生誕3DLIVE2025へようこそ！
Welcome to Hiodoshi Ao's Birthday 3D Live 2025!
はいよろこんで
Yes, gladly
あなた方の為
For your sake
はい謹んで
Yes, respectfully
あなた方の為に
For your sake
成し遂げてきたって
Even if I've achieved it
更なる正義だって
Even if it's further justice
嫌々で生き延びて
Surviving reluctantly
空回つやになって
Spinning my wheels
はいよろこんで
Yes, gladly
あなた方の為に
For your sake
できることなら
If I can
できるとこまで
As far as I can
足一歩踏み出して
Take a step forward
嫌な事思い出して
Remember the unpleasant things
奈落音頭奏でる
Playing the abyss dance music
ブンブンブン
Boom boom boom
もう一歩踏み出して
Take another step forward
嫌な事思い出して
Remember the unpleasant things
鳴らせ君の3から6マス
Sound your three to six squares
トントンツーツーツートントン
Dot dot dash dash dash dot dot dot
ギリギリダンス
Dancing on the edge
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス
Dancing on the edge
もっと鳴らせ
Sound it more
ギリギリダンス
Dancing on the edge
ぶっかけて等価が希望
I want equality in return
Service can be 伝えて
Tell me service can be
救われたのは
The one who was saved
僕の内の一人で
was one of the many "me"s
あと一歩踏み出して
Take one more step
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
鳴らせ音どこ奏でろ
Make a sound, play it somewhere
ブンブンブン
Boom boom boom
もう一歩踏み出して
Take another step
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
鳴らせ君の三から六マス 分かれ道思うがまま
Ring out your 3 to 6 spaces, at the crossroads just as you please
Go to明日 任せて霧はがままの言葉
Go to tomorrow, leave it to me, words like a fog of selfishness
さあ奏でろハクナマタタの音は
Now play the sound of Hakuna Matata
トントントンツーツーツートントン
Tap tap tap, dash dash dash, tap tap tap
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
On the edge dance, on the edge dance
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
On the edge dance, on the edge dance
もう鳴らせ
Ring it out already
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
On the edge dance, on the edge dance
踊れ
Dance
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス
On the edge dance, on the edge dance
もう鳴らせ
Ring it out already
鳴らせ君の病の街も どん
Ring out your city of illness, too (don)
覚醒笑える他人の不備も どん
Awaken, the imperfections of others you can laugh at, too (don)
ぐちゃる正義の超人たちも どん
The supermen of crumbling justice, too (don)
鳴らせ君の三から六マス トントントンツーツーツートントン
Ring out your 3 to 6 spaces, tap tap tap, dash dash dash, tap tap tap
はいよろこんで あなた方のために
Yes, with pleasure, for all of you
できることなら できるとこまで
If it's something I can do, as much as I can
はい謹んで あなた方のために
Yes, respectfully, for all of you
鳴らせ君の三から六マス トントントンツーツーツートントン
Ring out your 3 to 6 spaces, tap tap tap, dash dash dash, tap tap tap
やあ 溜めに溜めたフラストレーション パーッと開放するマスターベーション
Hey, that long-pent-up frustration, let it all out like masturbation
合法的トビ方のススメ
作詞:R-指定 作曲:DJ松永
The Recommendation of the Legal Way to Fly
Lyrics: R-Shitei Composition: DJ Matsunaga
どうしたの皆さんファーストデート みたいに緊張してるマスカレード
What's wrong everyone, like a first date, nervous masquerade
ポーカーフェイスの裏側でも 逃げない欲望渦巻いてさ
Even behind the poker face, unavoidable desires are swirling
パンクしそうならぶちまけろ 気持ちいいことしよう
If you're about to burst, let it all out, let's do something that feels good
ワンショット
One shot
詳細液体 はっきりとしない実態 それは期待か答え聞きたいか答え
Detailed liquid, an unclear reality, is that expectation or an answer? Do you want to hear an answer?
逝きたいと絶えずのたまう 君の期待に応え
Responding to your expectations, as you constantly say you want to go
砕いて裂いて巻いて焚いて 吸って吐いても
Even if you crush, tear, roll, burn, inhale, and exhale
増して炙っても打っても得られない 快感たまらずギブアップ
Even if you increase, toast, or inject, you won't get that pleasure, can't stand it, give up
エーオー 耳から体内に入る脳内を蝕み犯すポイズン
A-O, poison that enters through the ears and erodes the brain
再生するたび息吹き返す お前の価値観いじくり倒す
Each time it's played, it comes back to life, messing with your values
いつだってグルービーに君臨する世界の中央
Always reigning groovy at the center of the world
はまっちまったら終身刑 そのドラッグの名はミュージック
If you get hooked, it's a life sentence, the name of that drug is Music
高層ビルの谷間から 海の向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to beyond the sea
蔓延するセクシー・アンド・ロックンロール
Spreading sexy and rock 'n' roll
調教済みの豚どもは声上げろ
You trained pigs, raise your voices
超越するセクシー・アンド・ロックンロール
Transcending sexy and rock 'n' roll
とっくのとうに外れたブレーキ 逆らえない本能
The brakes came off long ago, instincts that can't be resisted
クリスタルメスもバッポヘッズも場末のヤッパロも
Whether it's crystal meth, bapo heads, or street-end junkies
なくても平気しちゃってもクレイジー 弾頭とマイクロフォンよこせ
Fine without it, crazy even if you do it, give me the warhead and the microphone
合法的なトビ方を心得よう
Let's learn the legal way to get high
花びら大回転咲き 枯れちまうくらい体を重ねてフライ
Flower petals spinning in full bloom, overlap bodies until you wither and fly
ヌードの夜踊る乙女の美貌 まだ凝りずにしがみ付く愛の理想
A maiden's beauty dancing in the nude night, still clinging to ideals of love without learning
恋情のこりそうな骨折り損 寄り添っちゃ突き放す氷の微笑
Wasted effort likely to leave lingering affection, an icy smile that snuggles then pushes away
ウブな振りして遊ばれよう 気持ちいいことしよう ワンショット
Pretend to be naive and be played with, let's do something that feels good, one shot
イン・アウト イン・アウト タイトなループでヒーヒー這わす
In out, in out, making you crawl and pant with a tight loop
高嶺の花様 お慕いしておりますから 押し倒して乗ります
Oh high-and-mighty flower, I adore you, so I'll push you down and ride
ノンセ・魅力は満点さ しぶき悪夢サブライムマンデー
Non-se, charm is perfect, splash nightmare sublime Monday
めっちゃエログロナンセンス 揺らした美尻アステオン・ラグジュア
Totally erotic-grotesque-nonsense, swinging that beautiful ass, asteon luxuria
そーりー ワンモアチャンス その不安もわかるけどワンモアチャンス
Sorry, one more chance, I understand that anxiety too, but one more chance
いつもはぐらかして たぶらかしてくる ファム・ファタールの名はミュージック
Always dodging and deceiving, the name of that femme fatale is Music
高層ビルの谷間から 海の向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to beyond the sea
蔓延するセクシー・アンド・ロックンロール
Spreading sexy and rock 'n' roll
調教済みの豚どもは声上げろ
You trained pigs, raise your voices
超越するセクシー・アンド・ロックンロール
Transcending sexy and rock 'n' roll
とっくのとうに外れたブレーキ 逆らえない本能
The brakes came off long ago, instincts that can't be resisted
クリスタルメスもバッポヘッズも場末のヤッパロも
Whether it's crystal meth, bapo heads, or street-end junkies
なくても平気しちゃってもクレイジー 弾頭とマイクロフォンよこせ
Fine without it, crazy even if you do it, give me the warhead and the microphone
合法的なトビ方を心得よう
Let's learn the legal way to get high
巻いて焚いて吸って吐いて 炙って打ってお構いねえぜ
Roll it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it, toast it, inject it, I don't give a damn
酔っ払って抱いて寄せて やめてよしとけ縁がねえぜ
Get drunk, hold me, draw me near, stop it, forget it, there's no fate here
洒落てなくて小汚くて 土臭くて品がねえぜ
Not chic, kinda dirty, earthy, and lacking class
みたいな奴らからはこれで飛び上げ
For folks like that, fly up with this
巻いて焚いて吸って吐いて 炙って打ってお構いねえぜ
Roll it, burn it, inhale it, exhale it, toast it, inject it, I don't give a damn
酔っ払って抱いて寄せて やめてよしとけ縁がねえぜ
Get drunk, hold me, draw me near, stop it, forget it, there's no fate here
洒落てなくて小汚くて 土臭くて品がねえぜ
Not chic, kinda dirty, earthy, and lacking class
ロクにロールもできねえなら ヒップにホップで飛んじまえばいい
If you can't even roll properly, just fly away with hip-hop
高層ビルの谷間から 海の向こう
From the valleys of skyscrapers to beyond the sea
蔓延するセクシー・アンド・ロックンロール
Spreading sexy and rock 'n' roll
調教済みの豚どもは声上げろ
You trained pigs, raise your voices
超越するセクシー・アンド・ロックンロール
Transcending sexy and rock 'n' roll
とっくのとうに外れたブレーキ 逆らえない本能
The brakes came off long ago, instincts that can't be resisted
クリスタルメスもバッポヘッズも場末のヤッパロも
Whether it's crystal meth, bapo heads, or street-end junkies
なくても平気しちゃってもクレイジー 弾頭とマイクロフォンよこせ
Fine without it, crazy even if you do it, give me the warhead and the microphone
合法的なトビ方を心得よう
Let's learn the legal way to get high
はい！ということで、
Alright! So,
誕生日だーーー！！
It's my birthday!!
自己紹介させていただきます。
Allow me to introduce myself.
えー、可愛い女の子かと思った？
Ee, did you think I was a cute girl?
じゃじゃーん！青くんでしたーー！
Ta-da! It was Ao-kun!
ホロライブデバイス、リグロスのボーイッシュ担当、火威青でーす。
I'm Hiodoshi Ao, in charge of 'boyish' for Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS.
今日は僕の3D生誕ライブに遊びに来てくれて、どうもありがとうーー！！
Thank you so much for coming to my 3D birthday live today!!
えー、ハッシュタグはこちら！
Ee, the hashtag is this one!
#火威青生誕3Dライブ2025
#HiodoshiAoBirthday3DLive2025
こちらで、スクショとかたくさん撮って、
Please take lots of screenshots with this hashtag,
僕のかっこいい顔面をパシャパシャパシャパシャして、
snap photos of my cool face over and over,
たくさんポストしてくださいねーー！わーーい！
and post them a lot! Yay!
ということで、1曲目は『はいよろこんで』
So, for the first song, 'Hai Yorokonde',
そのままえー『合法的トビ方のススメ』を歌わせていただきました。
followed by 'Gouhouteki Tobikata no Susume' were performed.
いやー、言いたいことはわかってる。
Yeah, I know what you want to say.
なんか、あ、踊るとかじゃないんだ。ここなんだ！って思ったと思います。
You probably thought, 'Oh, it's not about dancing, it's about this!'
ええ、そうです。
Yes, exactly.
ここです！
It's this!
いっぱいここの、ここの写真をいっぱい撮って、いっぱいポストしてくださいーーー！
Take lots of photos of this, right here, and post them everywhere!
おっ？なんか誰か来た！
Oh? Looks like someone's here!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
わーーー！
Whoa!
お邪魔しまーす！
Sorry to intrude!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
どうしたん、こんなちっちゃくなって！
What happened? You guys are so small!
来ちゃったーー！
We're here!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
おめでとーー！
あー、ちょっと来てくださった3人のプリンセスの自己紹介をしていただきましょうか。
Ah, let's have the three princesses who came here introduce themselves.
じゃ、身長小さい順から、どうぞ。
Well then, please go in order from shortest to tallest.
じゃあちっちゃい子からどうぞー。
Alright, let's start with the smallest one.
はいっ！
Yes!
一番ちっちゃい、え、ReGLOSS所属のURS-No.1005、轟と申します。お願いします！
The smallest one, uh, URS-No.1005 of ReGLOSS, I'm Todoroki. Nice to meet you!
あー、轟ちゃーん、これです！
Ah, Todoroki-chan, it's this!
もうちょっときっしー、もうちょっときっしー。
A little more Kishii, a little more Kishii.
次に、こっちかな？こっちこっちかな？次に小さい方。
Next, maybe this way? This way, this way? The next shortest person.
こっちは、えっと、Neo-Porte 3期生、悪魔教、その、昏昏アリアですよろしくお願いします。
As for me, I'm Neo-Porte 3rd Gen, Konkon Aria of the Devil's Cult. Nice to meet you.
あー、いいですねー。
Ah, that's good.
はい、にじさんじEN所属の狂蘭メロコでございます、よろしくお願いいたします。
Hello, I am Kyoran Meroko of Nijisanji EN. Pleased to meet you.
わーーい、一番デカ女でーす。
Yay, I'm the tallest woman here.
やったーー！いつもの場所よりデカいですよ。
Yay! I'm bigger than I usually am.
まぁ、一番デカいのは僕だから。
Well, I'm the tallest one here.
揉めるな。
Don't start a fight.
そんな変わらないだろ、私と。
There's not much difference between us.
変わる変わる、ごめん変わるわ。
There is, there is. Sorry, but there is.
それは変わるよ。
That's definitely a difference.
えー、ちょっと来てくれてありがとう。今日はあれですか？
Anyway, thank you for coming. So, today is...
僕を指名しに来てくれたんですか？
did you come here to choose me?
そうだよ。
That's right.
撮影会ね。
For the photo session.
そうだよ、可愛い青くん撮りに来た。
Yeah, we came to take photos of cute Ao-kun.
かっこいい青くん撮りに来てくれてありがとう。
Thank you for coming to take photos of 'cool' Ao-kun.
まぁ、かっこいい...どっちもね。
Well, cool... both are fine.
かっこいい、（かっこ）仮。
'Cool' (subject to change).
かっこいい真実。
Cool is the truth.
ということで、じゃ、せっかくだからお写真撮っていきましょうよ。
So, since we're here, let's take some photos.
いっぱい色んなポーズしてよ、ちょっと。
Give us lots of different poses!
任せて。ポーズ撮るのだけ生業にして生きてきたんだから。
Leave it to me. I've been living my life just for posing.
青くん 大はしゃぎにより 大幅カット！
※フルは後日公開！？
Ao-kun gets too excited, major cuts made!
*Full version to be released later!?
どうでした？でもなんか噂によるとみんなはさ、みんなもなんか僕のこの写真用の枠描いてきてくれたって聞いたんだけど。
How was that? But I heard a rumor that everyone drew custom photo frames for me.
描いてきたよ、見せちゃうじゃん、準備したい。
We did! Let us show you, let's get ready.
URS-No.1005 作
Created by URS-No.1005
どんなの？じゃあまず...
What's it like? Well first...
おっ！何これ！
Oh! What's this!
これ誰のこれ？
Whose is this?
この文字見たらわかる。
You can tell by looking at the handwriting.
え、すごい。これ、もしかして何これ、ひげ？
Wow, amazing. Is this... wait, what's this, a mustache?
ちょっとアップ、アップを見たいな。
Let's see a close-up, I want a close-up.
あー可愛い、ひげじゃない？
Ah, it's cute. Isn't it a mustache?
かっこいいな、かっこいいな。
It's cool, it's cool.
この眉毛下がるやつちょっとエッチだな。
The way the eyebrows go down is a bit sexy.
え、青くんキラキラ出せないの？
Hey Ao-kun, can't you make some sparkles?
あ、出せるよ。
Ah, I can.
おー、出た出た！いい、いい！
Oh, there they are! Good, good!
可愛い、かっこいい、かっこいい、かっこいい、可愛い。
Cute, cool, cool, cool, cute.
え、めっちゃいい！マジで。
Wow, this is great! Seriously.
めっちゃナンバーワン。
Totally number one.
これ普通に欲しい欲しい。
I honestly want this.
後で送って. 撮ってる撮ってる。
Send it to me later. I'm taking the picture.
最高のお写真撮れたよ。
I got the best photo.
ポストしなきゃ。
Gotta post it.
ナンバーワンをあなたに。
Giving 'number one' to you.
やったー！ナンバーワンポーズ来た。
Yay! There's the number one pose.
昏昏アリア 作
Created by Konkon Aria
はい、昏昏アリアが描いてきました。
Yes, Konkon Aria drew this.
あーん♡
Open wide~♡
うわこれ、え、これすごい。待って。
Whoa, this is... wow, amazing. Wait.
言ってあげて、言ってあげて。
Give her some praise, give her some praise.
あおくん、お誕生日おめでとう。
Ao-kun, happy birthday.
ケーキ、あ〜ん。
The cake, say "ah".
あ〜ん！あ〜ん！可愛い〜！
Ahhh! Say "ah"! So cute!
お前が本妻だよ、もう。
You're the real wife, honestly.
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
いっぱい食べてね。
Eat a lot, okay?
おいしい！
It's delicious!
いや、これ天才的だね。
Wow, this is genius.
これ天才だよね。
This is genius, right?
動きやめて。
Stop moving.
右見えてるから。
The right side is visible.
そりゃするのよ。
Well, I'm going to move.
狂蘭メロコ 作
Meloco Kyoran's Work
あおくん、おてしてごらん、おて。
Ao-kun, give me your hand. Hand.
私におてしてごらん。
Give me your hand.
これ...何？
What is... this?
おてでもっぽい！っぽい！
It's like a "hand" command! Like it!
おてでもいいし、顔のせてもいいだし。
A hand is fine, or you can put your face on it.
顔も乗るんだ。
My face goes on it too.
可愛い、これ。よしよしよし。
It's cute. Good boy, good boy.
よしよしよしよしよしよしよし。
There, there, there, there, there.
ちょっと悲しい顔したいけどね。
I want to make a sad face though.
複雑な顔してる。
You have a complicated look.
あ、それそれ！それが見たかった！
Ah, that's it! That's what I wanted to see!
なんだこれ。
What is this?
あおくんはやっぱ、大きい犬みたいなとこあるから。
Because you have that big dog-like side to you, Ao-kun.
違うよ。
I do not.
おてしてごらんって。いや、大きいイケメンだけどね。
Saying "give me your hand". Well, a big handsome guy though.
この状態でもう一枚見てほしいな。
I want to see one more in this state.
あ、じゃあこの状態からの、私もう一個持ってきたの。
Ah, well from this state... I brought one more thing.
プレゼント持ってきて。
Bring out the present.
すごいクオリティ高いのきたけどね。
A really high-quality one just arrived.
たんじょうび おめでとう！！
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!
はい、これうんち。はい、これうんち。
Here, it's poop. Here, it's poop.
やだー！あおくん！あおくん！
No way! Ao-kun! Ao-kun!
これ、うんち好きでしょ、あんた。なんで？
You like poop, don't you? Why?
あんたずっと「うんち、うんち」言ってんだから。
Because you're always saying "poop, poop".
僕は別にいいよ。これメロコ様のものってことでしょ？
I don't mind. This means it's Meloco-sama's, right?
そうそう、これ一番きれいなうんち持ってきた、今日。
Right, I brought the most beautiful poop today.
2025年で一番きれいだなと思って。
Thinking it's the most beautiful one of 2025.
まだ始まったばっかなんだよ。
The year has only just begun.
わーすごい。手に乗せて持ってきた。
Wow, amazing. I brought it on my palm.
ちょっとこれキラキラいらないだろ、ここ。
Hey, we don't need these sparkles here.
キラキラ消しとく、ほら、消すぞ。うんち好きじゃん、あんた。
I'll erase the sparkles. Look, I'm erasing them. You like poop, don't you?
なんで消すのや。
Why are you erasing them?
あ、うんち光ってるから、私すごい光らせてきた、今日。
Ah, because the poop is shining. I made it shine a lot today.
そっかそっかそっか。じゃあ二枚目。
I see, I see. Okay, the second one.
いらないです！あ、それ欲しかったやつ！
I don't want it! Ah, that's the one I wanted!
いい！いい！かっこいい！
Nice! Nice! So cool!
これいらないです。あ、それ欲しかったやつ！
I don't need this. Ah, that's the one I wanted!
ありがとう、ありがとう。何がめっちゃいいだ。
Thank you, thank you. What do you mean "so good"?
なんだ、ちょっと困らせたかった。
What, I just wanted to trouble you a bit.
たす...え、顔がいいな、おい。
He- wait, my face looks good.
顔がいいな、本当かっこいいな、あおたん。
Your face is good, you're really cool, Ao-tan.
あ、よかった。喜んでくれてよかった。
Ah, good. I'm glad you liked it.
うれしい、うれしい。
I'm happy, I'm happy.
コンコン、まだあるんじゃないの？
Kon-kon, isn't there more?
そう、私も二枚目あるんで。
Yes, I also have a second one.
そうなんだ！
Is that so!
見たい見たい！コンコン先生はちょっと信用度高いよ。
I want to see! I have high trust in Kon-kon-sensei.
がんばりました。最後に見よう、それ。
I worked hard. Let's see it at the end.
Part 2 昏昏アリア 作
Part 2 Aria Tasogare's Work
あ、やば！めっちゃピッタリじゃん！
Ah, wow! It fits perfectly!
それ、はまってるじゃん。
It's fitted on you.
なにこれ。知ってた？もしかして。
What is this? Did you know? Perhaps.
すごいすごい、はめ込んできたじゃん。
Amazing, amazing, you fitted it on.
はめ込みにきたんじゃないの。可愛い。
I didn't come here just to fit it on. It's cute.
あおくん、ちなみに...
Ao-kun, by the way...
下に小さいカメムシいるから、それは手に乗せる用だよ。
There's a small stink bug below, that's for your hand.
なんで、なんで芸が細かいんだよ。
Why, why is the detail so fine.
手のひらに。ここ？ここ？
On the palm. Here? Here?
あ、いい！いい！いい！さっきのよりか...
Ah, nice! Nice! Nice! Better than the last one...
メロコさんのうんちと...あれ、本当だ。
With Meloco-san's poop... oh, you're right.
これ、うんちと同じじゃん。
This is just like the poop.
これ合わせてきたわけじゃないんだ。
I didn't bring this to match.
こいつ合わせてきたから。あれ、こいつより...
Because I brought this to match. Wait, more than this...
デカいうんちだったけどな、完全に。
It was a huge poop, definitely.
写真撮れて嬉しいです。
I'm happy we could take photos.
ね、僕も嬉しかったよ。ありがとう。
Right, I was happy too. Thank you.
え、なんか疲れてない？大丈夫そう？
Eh, aren't you a bit tired? Are you okay?
大丈夫、これからだから。疲れてないよ、全然。
I'm fine, it's just starting. I'm not tired at all.
いや寝るな！寝るな！起きろ！起きろ！
Hey, don't sleep! Don't sleep! Wake up! Wake up!
はー、信じてたのに。
Sigh, and I believed in you.
まだゲストがいるんだぞ、ここに。
There are still guests here, you know.
寝るな！寝るな！そうでした、そうでした、王子様。
Don't sleep! Don't sleep! That's right, that's right, Prince.
このカメムシとうんちでビビってるようじゃ、ダメだよ、そりゃ。
If you're getting scared of stink bugs and poop, that's no good.
いや絶対いつか仕返ししてやるからな！
I'll definitely get back at you someday!
君たちが3Dになった暁には、僕もいたずらを仕掛ける。
When you guys get 3D models, I'll pull pranks on you too.
おー、なんか言ってる。しかもあれじゃない？
Oh, he's saying something. And isn't it also...?
せっかくだからさ、今日いないReGLOSSの面々も合わせて、
Since we're here, including the ReGLOSS members who aren't here today,
みんなでいつか3Dになったら、何か歌って踊ろうね。
let's sing and dance something together when we're all 3D.
やりたい！やろうね！絶対ですよ！
We want to! Let's do it! Definitely!
夢叶えよう、それみんなで。
Let's make that dream come true, all of us.
じゃあ最後にみんなで写真撮ろうか。
Well, shall we take a photo all together at the end?
オッケー！よいしょっと。写真撮れるな。
Okay! Heave-ho. We can take a photo.
撮れるな。え、これ、ひっくり返ってない？これ大丈夫だよね。
We can. Eh, is this upside down? It's okay, right?
よしよし、よしよし、よしよし。
There we go, there we go, there we go.
よしよし、よしよし、こういうことか。
There we go, there we go, so this is how it is.
え、何これ、知らない！知らない！
Eh, what is this? I didn't know! I didn't know!
知らない！三人のパネルあったんだ、待って。
I didn't know! There were panels of the three of them, wait.
これは知らないやつきた。
This is something I didn't know about.
え、よろしいんですか？これ。
Eh, is this okay? This.
おて、すごい、あ、メロコちゃん！
Hand, amazing, ah, Meloco-chan!
あぶ、メロコちゃんが倒れるところだった。
Whoa, Meloco-chan almost fell over.
わたし、メロコさん反対だよ。あ、メロコさん反対、反対、反対。
I'm- Meloco-san is backwards. Ah, Meloco-san is backwards.
やべやべ。やべ、ママ様にごめんなさいってね。
Oops, oops. Oops, I should apologize to Mama-sama.
こっち、こっち、こっち、こっち。ああ、いいね、いいね。
This way, this way, this way, this way. Ah, nice, nice.
ああ、いいね、写真撮ろう。
Ah, nice, let's take a photo.
え、やばいんじゃない？
Eh, isn't this crazy?
いや、身長差あるな。
Wow, there's quite a height difference.
身長差いいよね。いやあんまないだろ。
The height difference is nice. Well, there isn't much.
あるだろうがよ。一番あるだろうがよ。
There is! There's a huge difference!
あ、いいんじゃない？ なんか、いい写真なんじゃない？
Ah, isn't this good? Like, a good photo?
いい、いい！
Good, good!
コンコン、コンコンって感じかな？
Like "Kon-kon, kon-kon"?
お団子食べてる、髪の毛がね...
Eating dango, the hair...
シュークリームが... お団子食べてる...
Cream puff... eating dango...
ちょっとちっちゃいからね。
Because you're a bit small.
すいません、すいません。
Excuse me, excuse me.
ということで、はい。この、これ、これを記念撮影して、
So, yes. Let's take this commemorative photo,
最後にしましょうか。ということで。
and wrap it up. So...
はい。じゃあ、聞いていいですか？ お誕生日おめでとうって言ってもらっていいですか？
Yes. Then, can I ask you? Can you all say "Happy Birthday"?
はい。はい。
Yes. Yes.
じゃあ... せーの！
Then... ready, set!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！ 来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you! Thanks for coming!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
ありがとう！ バイバイ！
Thank you! Bye bye!
いつか3Dで！
Someday in 3D!
ぜったい叶える！
Will definitely make it happen!
お、お？ 俺？ マリンちゃん！
Oh, oh? Me? Marine-chan!
おい！
Hey!
んだこの店は！
What is this shop?!
え、見て見て見て。綺麗でしょ？ 作ってもらった。
Eh, look look look. Beautiful, right? I had it made.
あんさ、マリンは客か？！
Listen, is Marine a customer?!
違うよ！
No!
なあ、なんだか全部営業だったんだね。
Hey, so it was all just business, wasn't it?
なに言ってんの、なに言ってんの。あ、おもしろ。おもしろ。
What are you saying, what are you saying. Ah, funny. Funny.
本性... マリンちょっと落ち着け。
True nature... Marine, calm down a bit.
ほら、マリンちゃん。君のためのバラだよ。
Here, Marine-chan. A rose for you.
咲き誇れ！
Bloom proudly!
あー！ バラが！
Ah! The rose!
青くん。
Ao-kun.
はい。
Yes.
見て。
Look.
あ、うわっ！ なんてこともってきたんだ、これ。
Ah, whoa! What on earth did you bring?!
ほら、可愛いでしょ？
Look, it's cute, right?
可愛くない。
It's not cute.
見ててね。いくよ。はっ！
Watch this. Here I go. Ha!
うわぁぁぁ！
Uwaaa!
はい、これ。5秒後のお前の姿。
Here, this is you in 5 seconds.
ぎゃぁぁぁ！
Gyaaa!
それ、森へお帰り。
Now, go back to the forest.
あぁ！ カメムシ！
Ah! Stink bug!
今日がお前の命日。
Today is your anniversary of death.
ぎゃぁぁぁ！
Gyaaa!
てめぇ、嘘つき！ 全部営業だったんだな！
You... liar! So it was all just business!
あ、ごめん！
Ah, sorry!
俺も騙されてた！ お前に殺される！
I was deceived too! I'm gonna be killed by you!
何が誕生日だ、ふざけんなてめぇ！
What do you mean "birthday", don't mess with me, you!
落ち着いてマリンちゃん！
Calm down, Marine-chan!
スキ、キライ、ワカンナイ、キライ
Like, hate, I don't know, hate
スキ、ダ！
I like you!
ハイ、イガイ、アリエナイ、スキ、ダ！
Yes, unexpected, impossible, I like you!
スキ、ト、キライ、ワカンナイ
Between like and hate, I don't know
トマラナイ
It won't stop
スキ、キライ！
Like, hate!
スキキライ 作詞：フェルナンドP 作曲：ゴム
Love Hate | Lyrics: Ferdinand-P, Music: GOM
もー！ あいつの告白ってやつ
Jeez! That guy's confession
頭の中ぐるぐる回る
It's spinning around in my head
スキ、キライ、真ん中はあるの？
Like, hate, is there a middle?
迫られる二択
Forced to choose between two
もう、返事は決まってるはずさ
Geez, the answer should already be decided
「Wedding」
"Wedding"
そう、ビジョンは完璧！
Yes, the vision is perfect!
そうだ、住むのは、ショートあたりがいいな
That's right, living near a station would be good
子供は3人かなー
Maybe three kids?
待って、何で？ だって14歳ですよ？ ですよ！
Wait, why? I mean, I'm 14! I am!
「付き合うとか」
"Like dating..."
「スキ、ダ」
"I like you"
話聞いてバカ！
Listen to me, you idiot!
ノーガードだぜ、スキが多いの
No guard, you have many openings (suki)
恋してみたいわ、ふわふわと
I want to try falling in love, fluffily
あげるスピーチに詰まっている
Getting stuck on a speech I'm giving
パンダはシロクマで、シンクロまで
Panda is a polar bear, until we synchro
世界がはずむの
The world is bouncing
スキ、ト、キライ、ワカンナイ
Between like and hate, I don't know
キライ
Hate
デモ、スキ
But, I like you
ホイ！
Hoy!
え？
Eh?
レインボー、帰り道、欲しがってたやつ
Rainbow, the one you wanted on the way home
眺める君を僕は見ていた
I was watching you as you gazed at it
通学路、反対だけど
The way to school is the opposite direction, but...
それは気にしないで
...don't worry about that
てゆーか、あんまりスキじゃないタイプゆえに
I mean, since you're not really my type...
うぅ、反動でしょうか
...ugh, maybe it's a reaction?
そっか、急に優しくなんかされたから
I see, it's because you were suddenly kind to me
グラついて動揺
I'm wavering and upset
パッと、スッと引いて、冷静になってみても
Even if I suddenly, smoothly pull back and try to be calm
間違いなく
Without a doubt
理屈抜きで、スキ
Without any logic, I like you
ノープロブレム、僕を信じて
No problem, believe in me
ほら、君に火をつけた
Look, I set you on fire
ゆらゆらと燃えて灰になる
Burning waveringly and turning to ash
パイロマニア、愛しているんだ
Pyromania, I love you
...だけど　おそらく正解
...but it's probably the right answer.
やだなぁ　染められそう
Oh no, I might get dyed in your color.
知ってしまった優しさ
The kindness I've come to know.
時にヘンタイでも
Even if you're a pervert sometimes.
好きに染められてく
I'm being dyed by love.
恋してみたいわ　ギラギラ
I want to fall in love, dazzlingly.
とパンダが寝てちゃ　つまらない
It's boring if the panda is asleep.
愛して出して　水準上げて
Show your love and raise the bar.
初めて育つの
Then it'll grow for the first time.
ほう！
Ho!
ぶつかる二人　同時「好き」
Two people clashing, saying 'I love you' at the same time.
絡み合う二人の不安なら十
The intertwining anxieties of the two are ten-fold.
嫌いさえ
Even the 'hates'...
裏表
...are two sides of the same coin.
僕らいま
Right now, we are...
恋してる
...falling in love.
Yeah
Ho!
好きよ嫌いは合ってる　好きよ
I love you, 'hate' is just right, I love you.
好きよ嫌いありえない　好きだ
I love you, 'hate' is impossible, I love you.
好きと嫌いは終わらない　ララララ
Love and hate never end, la-la-la-la.
好き嫌い
Love-hate.
うわぁー！ギャー！
Uwaaa! Gyaaa!
恥ずかしい？
Are you embarrassed?
ちょっとね。
A little bit.
ちょっとね　ちょっとね。
Just a little, just a little.
青くんいくよ。せーの！
Ao-kun, here we go. One, two...!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
やったー！
Hooray!
おめでとう。
Congratulations.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
素敵な初めての青くんのバースデーライブですね。
It's a wonderful first birthday live for you, Ao-kun.
そうです！
That's right!
うぅー！
Woooo!
初めての、すごいいよ、見て！
The first one... it's amazing, look!
ねえ、すげえステージ。
Right? What an amazing stage.
すげえよこれ、見てほら、サイリウムも。
This is incredible, look at all the penlights too.
わー、え、これ店だよな？
Wow, wait, this is a club, isn't it?
おい、一回やるのかそのコント。
Hey, are you going to do that skit again?
やめてそのコント。
Stop that skit.
はい、喧嘩コントでした。
Yes, that was our fighting skit.
はい。
Yes.
でも。
But.
僕はやっぱり。
I, after all...
おお。
Oh.
この初めてのね、3Dライブでマリンちゃんと一緒に歌って踊れたこと...
...being able to sing and dance with Marine-chan in my very first 3D live...
うんうん。
Yeah, yeah.
マジ一生の宝物ってわけ。
...is truly a lifelong treasure.
チャチャッ！
Tcha-tcha!
でもこれあれ、うちらのこれからの挨拶これにしようよね。
But you know, let's make this our official greeting from now on.
あ、どうも。
Ah, hello.
青海です！イェーイ！
We are Ao-umi! Yay!
コントやってく？
Wanna keep the skit going?
はいどうもー！
Yes, hello there!
やだー。
No way.
やらね、一人でやってろマジで。
I'm not doing it, just do it by yourself, seriously.
なんでだよ！
Why not?!
青の真似。
My impression of Ao.
「失礼な！ブイー！」
"How rude! Veee!"
ねえ！人の誕生日のMCで暴れ散らかしております散らかしてるですね。
Hey! You're wreaking havoc during someone's birthday MC segment.
えー、ということで。
Well, on that note...
ということで。
...on that note.
え、あ、もう邪魔ですか？
Uh, oh, am I in the way now?
いやいや。
No, no.
このままここに住もうと思ってたんですけど。
I was thinking of just living here from now on.
あー、いいね。そうしたいことは山々なんだけど。
Ah, that's nice. I'd love that too, but...
いていいんだよねここに。
I can stay here, right?
何か見られてまずいものでも？
Is there something you don't want me to see?
そうじゃないけどね。
It's not that, but...
あ、そうじゃない、ポポポ。また一緒にこうやって歌って踊ってくれるかな？
Ah, that's not it, po-po-po. Will you sing and dance with me again like this?
つぎな！
Next time!
ギャー！
Gyaaa!
お誕生日おめでとうウィー！
Happy Birthday-wee!
ありがとうウィー！
Thank you-wee!
お前も言うんかい。お前も来んな。
You're saying it too? Don't you follow me either.
お腹空いた。
I'm hungry.
リリィの部屋
絶対観てね！！
Lily's Room
Make sure to watch!!
やっと一緒にステージ立てた！
世界一のハニー♡♡
これからもよろしくね
Finally stood on stage together!
The world's #1 honey ♡♡
Looking forward to more from now on
さて、次のプリンセスはっと...
Now then, the next princess is...
あ！ミオ先輩！
Ah! Mio-senpai!
青くーん！
Ao-kuuuun!
うわー！来てくれて嬉しい！
Waaa! I'm so happy you came!
呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you for inviting me!
イェーイ！
Yay!
おお、元気だなぁ。
Wow, you're full of energy.
僕も隣座っちゃおうかなーって。
I thought I'd come sit next to you.
え、何この素敵空間というか、なんかちょっとムーディーな感じ。
Eh, what is this wonderful space? It's got a bit of a moody vibe.
ムーディーでしょう。これはですね、なんと見てくださいよ。
It is moody, isn't it? Well, take a look at this.
じゃん！僕のお店！
Ta-da! My club!
おお、すごい！すごいね、めっちゃ豪華だ。
Oh, amazing! It's great, really luxurious.
お隣失礼しちゃって。
Pardon me for sitting next to you.
なんやかんや、こうやって二人で喋るのって...
Somehow, talking like this, just the two of us...
あんまないかも。
...doesn't happen very often.
確かにいつも、あれ？もう一人、あ、あれ？あ、あ、あ...
True, usually... wait? There's another person... ah, eh?
かっこいいガンボのもう一人が！いろはー、見てるかー！いろは先輩！師匠！師匠！
The other member of Cool Gumbo! Iroha, are you watching?! Iroha-senpai! Master! Master!
いや、今回は二人ですけど、いつかはね、三人でも何かやりたいですね。
Well, it's just the two of us this time, but someday, I want to do something with all three of us.
いろは一緒に歌おうな今度は！歌おー！
Iroha, let's sing together next time! Let's sing!
よろしくお願いします！
We're counting on you!
あっ、そういえば青くん誕生日おめでとう。
Ah, by the way, Happy Birthday Ao-kun.
ありがとうございます！あ、忘れてた僕誕生日か。
Thank you very much! Ah, I forgot, it is my birthday.
あ、そうだった。
Oh, that's right.
そうだよ。誕生日だから呼んだんでしょ、ここに。結局。
Right. You invited me here because it's your
birthday, after all.
あ、そうなんです。やったー！
Ah, that's right. Yay!
今日だよ。イェイ！やったやった！
It's today! Yay! Yay, yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
あ、ところで、ちょっと気になってること聞いてもいい？
Ah, by the way, can I ask you something
I'm curious about?
もちろんですよ。
Of course.
何でも聞いてください。えっ？
Please ask me anything. Eh?
足元にいるの何？
What's that at your feet?
あ、あ、聞いちゃいます？
Ah, ah, you're going to ask?
えっ、えっ、えっ、えっ、えっ、えっ。
Eh? Eh? Eh...
聞いちゃいます？
You're going to ask?
えっ。
Eh?
あんなデッカイのが家に出たってこと？
Does that mean something that big showed up
at your house?
ちゃうちゃうちゃうちゃう。
No, no, no, no.
そりゃ騒ぐわ。
Then it's no wonder you made a fuss.
家に出たのは、本当にこんなんだったけど、
The one that showed up at home was actually
about this big, but...
あれは、誇張表現されたカメムシってこと？
Does that mean that's an exaggerated stink bug?
そうです。スタッフさんの悪ふざけですね。
That's right. It's the staff's prank.
えー、いらないって言ったけど、うん。
I said I didn't need it, but...
なんか、スタッフのお姉さんが「えー？」
But the staff lady was like, "Ehh?"
「せっかく作ったけど本当に？いらない？あれ？」って言われて、
"I went through the trouble of making it, but
really? You don't want it? Oh?"
「いります」って言っちゃった。
"I'll take it," I ended up saying.
「いる」って言っちゃった？
You said you wanted it?
言っちゃった。
I said it.
色仕掛けだ！いや、カメ仕掛け。
It's a honey trap! No, a "stink bug" trap.
カメ仕掛け、カメ仕掛け。
A stink bug trap, a stink bug trap.
なんかかっこいいな。カメ仕掛けだね。はい。
That sounds kind of cool. It's a stink bug trap. Yes.
え、なんかさ、うちはさ、こうやってさ、
Um, so, for me, you know...
こう、青くんの何て言うんだろう、ホストみたいな感じの企画やったりしてるよね？
Doing projects like, how should I say,
Ao-kun being like a host?
そうですね。一応やらせていただきますね。
That's right. I do it occasionally.
それでなんかこう接客を受けたことがうちはなくて、お店に行ったことがないから、
But I've never actually received that kind of service
because I've never been to the club.
あー。
Ah...
なるほど。うん。
I see. Yeah.
でもこちら実はですね、はい。
Actually, you see...
ホストではなくて、え？普通のバーなんですね。
It's not a host club, it's... eh? It's just a regular bar.
あ、そうなんだ！違うんだ。
Oh, is that so! It's different.
一番最初のホストクラブでやってこうかなって思ったけど、
I thought about doing it at a host club at first, but...
なんかホロメンの先輩方、リグロス含め向いてないなって思って。
I thought my Hololive senpais, including ReGLOSS,
aren't suited for it.
え、じわじわじわ。受ける側として向いてないってこと？
Eh, (laughs). You mean as customers they're not suited?
なんか、ちょっと空気違うなって。で、普通に飲み屋にしました。ええ。
I felt the vibe was a bit off. So I just made it
a regular drinking spot. Yeah.
あ、そうなんだ。ええ。
Oh, I see. Yeah.
せっかくだからなんかそういう接客みたいな、
Since we're here, maybe some of that service...
え？
Eh?
欲しいですよね？
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
やってくれるんですか？もちろんですよ。ホストクラブっぽいことではないですけど、
Will you do it? Of course. It's not host club-like,
but...
僕、あれできます。
I can do *that*.
え、どれ？
Eh, what?
イリュージョンができます。
I can do an illusion.
え、イリュージョン！？はい。見ますか？
Eh, an illusion!? Yes. Do you want to see?
見たい！やってやって！
I want to see! Do it, do it!
え、よいしょよいしょ... 何系何系？
Eh, heave-ho, heave-ho... What kind? What kind?
トランプ口からベロベロ系？こう。
Like spitting cards out of your mouth?
Like this.
おー！口からバラが！かっこいい！
Oh! A rose from your mouth! Cool!
かっこいい！イェーイ！
Cool! Yay!
それ口から出す時にさ、口の中ズタズタになんなかった？大丈夫？
When you put that in your mouth, didn't it tear
up the inside? Are you okay?
意外と、あの、取っちゃえばいける。
Surprisingly, if you remove *those*, it's fine.
あ、大丈夫？ええ。トゲトゲ取っちゃえばいける。
Oh, you're okay? Yeah. If you take the thorns
off, it's fine.
トゲ意外とポリって取れるんです。あ、そっかそっか。
The thorns actually come off with a snap.
Oh, I see, I see.
ポリって取って、加えればオッケー。オッケーオッケーね。
Snap them off and put it in, then you're okay.
Okay, okay.
でもやっぱり僕たち、はい。このようにかっこいい二人。
But after all, we... yes. We're two cool people
like this.
おお、かっこいいコンボですか。そう。
Oh, a cool combo? Yes.
かっこいい歌、おお、歌いたい。
A cool song... oh, I want to sing one.
かっこいい歌！かっこいい歌！二人で！
A cool song! A cool song! The two of us!
今日はいろは先輩はいませんが、僕たち二人でかっこいい歌を歌って、
Iroha-senpai isn't here today, but the two of us
will sing a cool song.
僕も王子様。澪先輩も王子様。
I'm a prince. Mio-senpai is also a prince.
うちも！？
Me too!?
そう。二人でかっこよくなろうと思います。おおー！
That's right. I want the two of us to be cool.
Ohhh!
歌うぞー！イェーイ！うちもかっこよく歌うぞ！やったー！
Let's sing! Yay! I'll sing coolly too! Yay!
王子様、二人いてもいいものなのかな。まあいっか。
Is it okay to have two princes? Well, whatever.
あ、国の数だけあるんで。あ、そっかそっかそっか。
Ah, there are as many as there are countries.
Oh, right, right, right.
伝説の朝に 誓った言葉
The words vowed on that legendary morning
分かち合う声に 奇跡を照らせ
In the voices we share, let the miracles shine
革命を
Revolution...
Let's shout!
革命を Let's shout!
Revolution, Let's shout!
風の舞う光の空
The sky of light where the wind dances
吹き抜ける残響
The reverberation blowing through
この右手と この左手
This right hand and this left hand
何を求める？
What do they seek?
魂のカタルシスに
In the catharsis of the soul
焦がれた感情
The emotions I yearned for
重ね合えば 繋ぎ合えば
If we overlap, if we connect
伝うのか
Will they reach you?
運命に委ね
Entrusting to fate
流れのままに
Just as the flow goes
変わらぬビジョンじゃ
With an unchanging vision
面白くない
It's not interesting
沸騰せよ 血液のレイ
Boil over, the ray of blood
交錯する 蜘蛛の糸のように
Intersecting like a spider's web
革命のデュアリズム
Dualism of Revolution
さあ、始めよう
Come, let's begin
以心伝心 生の咆哮 届いていますか？
Telepathy, the roar of life, is it reaching you?
化学反応 愛の伝承
Chemical reaction, the legend of love
付いて来い 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of the dream
どんなロードだって
No matter what road it is
いつかは交わり ひとつに
Someday they will cross and become one
君をジャッジメントする
I will judge you
革命を Let's shout!
Revolution, Let's shout!
奇跡を奪え
Seize the miracle
痛みをぼかして
Blur the pain
何を守り 何を信じ
What to protect, what to believe in...
生きろと言う
...tell me to live.
未来へのドアは 鋼のタフさ
The door to the future has the toughness of steel
残酷を選べ 暁の君
Choose cruelty, youth of the dawn
指の掛かる 行ったことない
At my fingertips, where you've never been...
絶景のBlue 教えてやる
...I'll show you the breathtaking Blue
覚醒のデュアリズム
Dualism of awakening
さあ飛び込め
Now dive in!
鮮やかなハレーション 火花を散らして
A vivid halation, scattering sparks
無限のブレード 叩き込め
Drive in the infinite blade
どこまで行けるのか
How far can we go?
変わらない何かの手
With an unchanging hand
何度口づけした そして
No matter how many times we kissed, then...
君は まばゆいに出会う
...you will encounter the radiance
Just my heart...
Just is...
誇り高き愛の結晶
A crystal of prideful love
握り締めたら 迎えに行くから
Once I grasp it, I'll come for you
いつから一緒さ 全て見せてきた
We've been together since when? I've shown you everything
君へのラブソング
My love song to you
Break up 鎖引きちぎって 独立せよ
Break up, tear the chains apart and become independent
一心同体の咆哮 届いて今
Let the roar of two hearts as one reach you now
加速する愛の鼓動 ついて来い
The accelerating heartbeat of love, follow me
夢の果て
To the edge of dreams
何度だって いつかは交わり あの日
Time and again, we will eventually cross paths; on that day...
君は ジャッジメントする
...you will pass your judgment.
革命を Let's shout!
Let's shout for the revolution!
No.1 カッコイイコンビ✨
次は3人で🎤
ミオ先輩
No. 1 Coolest Duo ✨
Next time with three people 🎤
Mio-senpai
リベンジ！ぜったい叶えようね
ハッピー！お誕生日おめでとう これからもよろしくね
Revenge! Let's definitely make it come true
Happy! Happy birthday, looking forward to working with you
心の中に いつもいつも 描いてる
Inside my heart, always, always, I'm drawing
（描いてる）
(I'm drawing)
夢を乗せた 自分だけの 世界地図
A world map of my own, carrying my dreams
タケコプター！
Bamboo Copter!
空を飛んで 時を越えて 遠い国でも
Flying through the sky, crossing through time, even to far-off lands
ドアを開けて ほら 行きたいよ 今すぐ
Open the door and look, I want to go right now
どこでもドア！
Anywhere Door!
大人になったら 忘れちゃうのかな
I wonder if I'll forget when I become an adult
そんな時には 思い出してみよう
At times like those, let's try and remember
シャララララ 僕の心に いつまでも 輝く夢
Sha-la-la-la-la, inside my heart, a dream that shines forever
ドラえもん そのポケットで かなえさせてね
Doraemon, make them come true with that pocket of yours
シャララララ 歌を歌おう みんなでさ 手をつないで
Sha-la-la-la-la, let's sing a song, everyone, hand in hand
ドラえもん 世界中に 夢を そう あふれさせて
Doraemon, let dreams overflow throughout the world
やりたいこと 行きたい場所 見つけたら
When I find things I want to do and places I want to go
（見つけたら）
(When I find them)
迷わないで 靴を履いて 出かけよう
Without hesitating, I'll put on my shoes and head out
タイムマシン！
Time Machine!
大丈夫さ 一人じゃない 僕がいるから
It'll be okay, you're not alone because I'm here
キラキラ輝く 宝物探そうよ
Let's search for sparkling treasures
四次元ポケット！
4D Pocket!
道に迷っても 泣かないでいいよ
Even if you get lost, it's okay not to cry
秘密の道具で 助けてあげるよ
I'll help you with my secret gadgets
シャララララ 口笛吹いて 高らかに 歩き出そう
Sha-la-la-la-la, whistling a tune, let's start walking with heads held high
ドラえもん あの街まで 届けばいいね
Doraemon, I hope it reaches all the way to that town
シャララララ
Sha-la-la-la-la
僕らの未来
Our future
夢がいっぱいあふれてるよ
Is overflowing with dreams
ドラえもん
Doraemon
君がいればみんな
When you're here, everyone
笑顔になる
Will be smiling
大人になってもきっと忘れない
Even when I grow up, I won't ever forget
大切な思いいつまでもずっと
These precious feelings, forever and always
シャララララ
Sha-la-la-la-la
僕の心に
In my heart
いつまでも輝く夢
A dream that shines forever
ドラえもん
Doraemon
そのポケットで叶えさせてね
Please make it come true with that pocket
シャララララ
Sha-la-la-la-la
歌を歌おう
Let's sing a song
みんなでさあ手をつないで
Come on, everyone, let's hold hands
ドラえもん
Doraemon
世界中に
All over the world
夢をそうあふれさせて
Fill the world with dreams
またあそびましょう
ソロライブヤッホー！！だね
フブキ先輩
Let's play again
Solo live, yahoo!!, right?
Fubuki-senpai
つまんないです
It's boring
散々です
It's terrible
既定路線
The predetermined course
がんばるだけの人生
A life of just working hard
Watch me dut-tu-lu-tu-tu-tu-choose 独りなしのmagic
Watch me dut-tu-lu-tu-tu-tu-choose magic without being alone
I wanna be free
だってもっと不埒
Because it's more outrageous
Shut it up, the end is the start
ヘイ、タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey, taxi, take me to space
宵を舞う もっと踊ってて
Dancing through the evening, keep on dancing
夜を急かす 魔物のように
Like a monster rushing the night
彗星は 一瞬にして
A comet, in an instant
溶ける魔法 それならば駆け抜けて思い通り
Is melting magic, so then run through it just as you wish
お邪魔な馬車飛び乗って Step by step
Jump on that annoying carriage, step by step
あたしは大変身メーカー
I'm a great transformation maker
我がままの マニマニ 煌めきにチュチュ
Selfish as can be, kissing the sparkle
狭くなった街で Dancing
Dancing in the narrowed town
さよならグッバイレトロカー
Goodbye, goodbye retro car
いつかは完成クラブオーディエンス 皆ご唱和あれ
Someday the club audience will be complete, everyone sing along
ビビデバビビデブーワ ビビデバビビデブーワ yeah
Bibideba bibidebouwa bibideba bibidebouwa yeah
こんがらがってもしょうがない ガラスシューズで踊らナイト
Can't be helped even if you're confused, gotta dance with glass shoes tonight
ビビデバビビデブーワ ビビデバビビデブーワ yeah
Bibideba bibidebouwa bibideba bibidebouwa yeah
今夜に明日などないならば 自由に踊ったもん勝ちでしょう？
If there's no tomorrow for tonight, the one who dances freely wins, right?
ダーダッダッダンス ラリラリホー
Da-da-da-dance La-ri-la-ri-ho
どんな問題も会話ひとつ
Any problem can be solved with one conversation
白紙も世界も間違いも
The blank paper, the world, even the mistakes
ああ本当のあたしの理想 なんだか世界は
Ah, my true ideal Somehow the world
限界の気配がして
Feels like it's at its limit
おたたたた 安心 ぜしんぱい 今すぐジャンピンジャンピンアップ
O-ta-ta-ta-ta, relax, don't worry Jumpin' jumpin' up right now
チェキチェキバンバン チェキバンバン
Cheki-cheki bang-bang, cheki-bang-bang
エタタクニキキカイタク
E-ta-ta-ku-ni-ki-ki-kai-ta-ku
日々にギリギリバカンス キミとたった今
On the edge of vacation in daily life, with you right now
発散してしまおうか
Shall we just blow it off?
まだまだビビたん 巧みに乱射
Still a bit scared Skillfully firing away
一発じゃ撃ち足りないわ
One shot isn't enough
ついに導き出したキミにアンサー ハイになるまで踊ってよ
Finally deduced the answer for you Dance until you're high
ビビデバビビデブーワ ビビデバビビデブーワ yeah
Bibideba bibidebouwa bibideba bibidebouwa yeah
お邪魔な馬車飛び乗って Step by step
Jump on that annoying carriage, step by step
あたしは大変身メーカー
I'm a great transformation maker
我がままの マニマニ 煌めきにチュチュ
Selfish as can be, kissing the sparkle
狭くなった街で Dancing
Dancing in the narrowed town
さよならグッバイレトロカー
Goodbye, goodbye retro car
いつかは完成クラブオーディエンス 皆ご唱和あれ
Someday the club audience will be complete, everyone sing along
ビビデバビビデブーワ ビビデバビビデブーワ yeah
Bibideba bibidebouwa bibideba bibidebouwa yeah
こんがらがってもしょうがない ガラスシューズで撮るナイト
Can't be helped even if you're confused, take pictures with glass shoes tonight
ビビデバビビデブーワ ビビデバビビデブーワ yeah
Bibideba bibidebouwa bibideba bibidebouwa yeah
今夜に明日などないならば 自由に踊ったもん勝ちでしょう？
If there's no tomorrow for tonight, the one who dances freely wins, right?
おかゆ先輩
ちっちゃくてカワイイ...
Okayu-senpai
Tiny and cute...
さあ、誕生日楽しかった！
Well, that birthday was fun!
ゲストもたくさん来てくれて、最高の誕生日だ。
So many guests came, it's the best birthday.
さあ...
Well...
お誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy Birthday!
おおー、びっくりしたあ...
Whoa, you scared me...
最高！おめでとう！
Awesome! Congratulations!
ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much. Thank you.
あ、じゃあ自己紹介するか？
Ah, shall we introduce ourselves?
うん。
Yeah.
いくぞ！レジトップ！We are...
Here we go! Regi-top! We are...
ReGLOSS!
全然違うんだよ。
That's not it at all.
え、なんで？こうじゃないの？
Eh, why? Isn't it like this?
俺らいつこれが揃うんだよ...
When are we ever going to get this in sync...?
ま、いっか。せっかくなんで自己紹介お願いいたします。
Well, whatever. Since we're here, please introduce yourselves.
はーい！
Okay!
じゃあ奏からいきます！
I'll go first then!
たまたま友達に誘われてライブ会場に来てみたら...
I happened to be invited by a friend and came to a live venue...
あれ、青さんの誕生日ライブでした！
Wait, it turned out to be Ao-san's birthday live!
おめでとう！ラッキーガール！イェーイ！
Congratulations! Lucky girl! Yay!
そして？
And?
はーい、どうも！可愛いポジティブジーニアス、一条莉々華だよ！
Hi there! I'm the cute positive genius, Ichijou Ririka!
家でゲームをしてて、「ああ、このイケメン画面から出てこないかな」って...
I was playing games at home, thinking 'Man, I wish this handsome guy would come out of the screen'...
画面を割ったらここに繋がっちゃったみたい！わあ！
...and when I broke the screen, it seems I got connected here! Wow!
ゲームの中から？！これ褒められてんのこれ？
From inside a game?! Is that supposed to be a compliment?
ま、いっか。そして？
Well, whatever. And?
はい！儒烏風亭一番は、ReGLOSSの賑やかしネタ枠担当、儒烏風亭らでんでございます！
Yes! Juufuutei number one, the one in charge of ReGLOSS's noisy gags, Juufuutei Raden!
えっと、シャンパンの伝票がこちらになりますので...
Um, here is the slip for the champagne...
あ、ありがとうございます。あ、カゴに置いときます。
Ah, thank you. I'll just put it in the basket.
なになに？シャンパン下ろしたの、らでんちゃんが？
What? Did Raden-chan order champagne?
おいこら！あああ...
Hey! Aaa...
そして？
And?
プンプンプン！ReGLOSSの番長、轟はじめれっち！
Pun-pun-pun! ReGLOSS's leader, Todoroki Hajime-lecch!
なんかポーズ可愛いな。今？
That pose is kinda cute. Is it new?
ずっとやってるよ！あ、そうなの？
She's been doing it! Oh, really?
今初めて視認したわ。お披露目からずっとやってるよ。
I just noticed it for the first time. I've been doing it since debut.
やってたよ！やばい。
She was doing it! No way.
で？こんちゃ、この流れがちょっともうわかんなくなっちゃってる...
And? Hello... I don't really get this flow anymore...
クチョから生まれた、轟はじめれっち！
Born from a beetle, Todoroki Hajime-lecch!
クチョから生まれたんだ。あ、ありがとう。
So you were born from a beetle. Ah, thanks.
生まれてきてくれてありがとう。ガラスの靴やな。
Thanks for being born. Glass slippers, huh.
ちょっと姫姫ってことやね。なるほどですね。
So you're like a princess. I see.
てかステージめっちゃいいやん！
Anyway, the stage is great!
どうしょこれ！Blue Fireってこと？そう！
Look at this! Is it Blue Fire? Yes!
あのなんか、乙待ちとかで使ったあれ...大丈夫かな？
Um, the stuff used for Otsumachi... is it okay?
なんか不安だな。すごい！乙待ち思い出すね！
I'm a bit worried. Amazing! It reminds me of Otsumachi!
ちょっと思い出さないでほしいけどね、それは。
I'd rather you didn't remember that, though.
いいよ、これ！あ、いいでしょうその椅子。
This is good! Ah, that chair is nice, isn't it.
え、なにしてんの？なにしてんの？
Eh, what are you doing? What are you doing?
わあ！奏ちゃん！
Whoa! Kanade-chan!
暴れてる！暴れてる！え、待って、でもお酒はあるよ。
She's going wild! Going wild! Wait, but we have alcohol.
お酒飲んでもいい？誰か止めて！誰か止めて！
Can I drink? Someone stop her! Someone stop her!
おいしー！あ、あ、ああ...
It's good! Ah, ah, aaa...
莉々華ちゃん！待て待て！やってないやってないって！
Ririka-chan! Wait wait! Don't do it!
言ってるだろうが！あー！
I told you not to! Aah!
どうするのこの後の段々...
What are we going to do about the next part...?
奏！何してんだよ！
Kanade! What are you doing!
バイオレンス！
Violence!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんで、もう破天荒なこと...そんなことやろうとしてない！
Why such reckless things... I didn't plan for any of this!
えい！えい！えい！えい！
Ei! Ei! Ei! Ei!
まどまど！らでんちゃん！ごめん、それもうみんなやってる。
Wait! Raden-chan! Sorry, everyone's already doing that.
（無言）
(Silence)
あ、それもやってる。ああ...
Ah, that's also been done. Aah...
でも番長はね...番長はもう何もやらないよね？
But Bancho... Bancho won't do anything, right?
信じてるよ、番長。さすがにね。
I trust you, Bancho. As expected.
あー！やー！
Ah! Yaah!
これ高いのに！めっちゃ綺麗なんだよ！
This was expensive! It's so beautiful!
暴れるな暴れるな！あー！
Don't go wild! Aah!
おい！青くんが壊した！破天荒になっちゃった！
Hey! Ao-kun broke it! He's gone reckless!
あーあ...この後もまだまだあったのに...もう終わりだね。
Aah... there was still so much more to come... it's over now.
終わりだね。終わりじゃない！
It's over. No it's not!
お前たち全員、この後ステージ...お疲れ様でした！
All of you, after this on stage... Good job today!
台本あんねん！聞け！
I have a script! Listen!
この後もステージ直すの、君たちにも手伝ってもらうからな！
You're going to help me fix the stage afterwards too!
えーー？！
Eeeeh?!
ということで。しょうがないな。
And so. It can't be helped.
なんかすごい賑やかですけれども...ま、一生言うか。
It's quite lively, but... well, let's just say it.
この生誕祭はゴリゴリだ！
This birthday festival is hardcore!
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて
Memeshikute, Memeshikute, Memeshikute
辛いよー！
It's painful!
僕の事からかったの？あんなに「好き」と言ったのに
Were you just teasing me? Even though you said you 'liked' me so much
奴のどこを気に入ったの？
What did you see in that guy?
僕はもういらない
I'm no longer needed
君と手をつなぎ踊りたい
I want to hold hands and dance with you
たくさんの人混みの中で
In the middle of a large crowd
君の笑顔だけが輝いて
Only your smile is shining
Hey!
愛されたいね　きっと見過ごした君のシグナルもう一度
I want to be loved; I surely missed your signal, one more time
Hey!
気紛れから　でも構わない　君といたいから
Even if it's just a whim, I don't care, because I want to be with you
Ah...
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
光を浴びて
Bathing in light
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
恋の歌 歌って
Singing a love song
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
いざ辿り着いたこの世界はもう
The world I've finally reached is already...
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, unmanly, unmanly
つらいよ
It's painful
今日は踊ろう　明日は忘れよう
Let's dance today, let's forget about tomorrow
昨日の古い悩みなど
Such as yesterday's old worries
君は誰を　次は誰と　心を組み交わす
Who will you, who will you exchange hearts with next?
本当は抱き合って眠りたい
Truth is, I want to embrace you and sleep
カラカラに乾いた心を
This bone-dry heart...
君の美しさで潤して
...moisten it with your beauty
Hey!
恋に焦がれ　いつもミスをした　女心雲のよう
Longing for love, I always made mistakes; a woman's heart is like a cloud
Hey!
晴れ渡れば　狭い心が　また浮ついている
If it clears up, my narrow heart will start fluttering again
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
二人を見つめ
Staring at the two of you
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
君が笑顔で
With you smiling...
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
奴の手（て）に触（ふ）れたこの胸（むね）はもう
...having touched his hand, my heart is already...
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, unmanly, unmanly
つらいよ
It's painful
OK! EVERYBODY!
楽しまなきゃ生きてる損なんだけど
If you don't enjoy yourself, it's a waste to be alive...
楽しいばかりじゃいられない
But it's not always just fun
生まれてきてごめんねって言いたい
I want to say "sorry for being born"
でも等身大
But I'm being my true self
ギターソロ！
Guitar solo!
Hey!
愛情と言う形ない君が欲しい　僕の心犬のよう
I want you, who has the formless shape of love; my heart is like a dog
騙されたって　どうぞ構わない　君といれるなら
I don't care even if I'm being deceived, as long as I can be with you
愛されたいね　きっと見過ごした君のシグナルもう一度
I want to be loved; I surely missed your signal, one more time
気紛れから　でも構わない　君といたいから
Even if it's just a whim, I don't care, because I want to be with you
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
光を浴びて
Bathing in light
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
恋の歌 歌って
Singing a love song
女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, I'm unmanly
いざ辿り着いたこの世界はもう
The world I've finally reached is already...
女々しくて 女々しくて 女々しくて
I'm unmanly, unmanly, unmanly
つらいよ
It's painful
ステージが治ったー！
The stage is fixed!
治んなくていいものも治ってるけど...
Things that didn't need to be fixed are also fixed, but...
まぁいいか。はい、ということで
Oh well. Okay, so...
次が最後の曲になります。
The next song will be the last one.
僕の始めてのオリジナル曲です。
It's my first original song.
聴いてください。クラブ・ブルーファイア。
Please listen. Club Blue Fire.
あ、久しぶり。
Ah, it's been a while.
早く君が来ないかなって、ずっと待ってたんだ。
I've been waiting for you all this time, wondering when you'd arrive.
ようこそ、Club Blue Fireへ。
Welcome to Club Blue Fire.
Club Blue Fire
作詞・作曲・編曲 中村歩 / 野口大志
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Ayumu Nakamura / Taishi Noguchi
お客様さあどうぞ
Customer, please come this way
VIPのお席へ
To the VIP seat
手始めにハイボールを
To start with, a highball
飲み干したら始めましょう
Once you've finished it, let's begin
足りない足りない酔えてない
Not enough, not enough, not drunk yet
飛び交う怒号のシャンパンコール
The roaring champagne calls flying around
つれない？つれない？んなこたぁ無い
Cold? Unfriendly? No such thing
不機嫌な姫にアルコール
Alcohol for the grumpy princess
よそ見しないで 僕を選んで
Don't look away, choose me
夜に溺れてしまう前に
Before we get drowned in the night
疑わないで 二人抜け出そう
Don't doubt it, let's sneak out together
いっそ
Rather...
今宵、皆Party さあParty 踊り明かそう
Tonight, everyone's at a party, let's party, dance all night
ふらついてるHoneyからCalling
Calling from a staggering Honey
Tonight Tonight Tonight...自問自答
Tonight Tonight Tonight... self-questioning
この世は天国か？それとも地獄か？
Is this world heaven? Or hell?
正解などないんじゃない 音に乗っかって Come on!
There might be no right answer, get on the sound, Come on!
馬鹿になっていいじゃない？
It's okay to be a fool, isn't it?
僕らはまだ
We are still...
足りてないって、酔えてない
Not enough, not drunk enough
(Welcome to the "Blue Fire")
Stop! こっからがShow time ご注目 ご静聴 It's Alright? (Hahaha)
Stop! From here it's show time, attention please, quiet please, It's Alright? (Hahaha)
卓越 突き刺した君のEyesから感じ自制心 凍る脳内
Excellence, I feel your eyes piercing through me, self-control freezes in my brain
終わらない止まらない Saturday Night 独占欲渦巻くホール
Non-stop, never-ending Saturday Night, a hall swirling with possessiveness
勘違い 泣き出す 暴れ出す 混沌 照らしな ミラーボール
Misunderstanding, crying out, going wild, mirror ball, light up the chaos
僕の目を見て ほら、手握って？
Look into my eyes, here, take my hand?
“出会った場所が此処だっただけ”だろ
It was just that this was the place where we met, right?
誰にも言えない 約束をしよう そっと
Let's make a secret promise, quietly
今宵、皆Party さあParty 酔い痺れそう
Tonight, everyone's at a party, let's party, I'm about to get drunk and numb
ギラついてるシャンデリア仰ぎ
Looking up at the glitzy chandelier
Tonight Tonight Tonight...自問自答
Tonight Tonight Tonight... self-questioning
天使の囁きか？悪魔の誘惑か？
Is it an angel's whisper? Or a devil's temptation?
判断力などもう無い 本性晒しちゃって Come on!
No more judgment left, reveal your true self, Come on!
さあさあ！こちら VIP 1番テーブルにお座りの
Now now! Over here at the VIP table number one
素敵な素敵な火女（ひめ）様から！なんと！シャンパンタワーいただきました！
From a lovely, lovely Princess! Wow! We received a champagne tower!
本日の王子、青くんから姫様へ感謝の気持ちを込めまして
From today's Prince, Ao-kun, with feelings of gratitude for the Princess
シャンパンコール 送らせていただきます！
I'll send you a champagne call!
今夜は！ (今夜は！)
Tonight! (Tonight!)
貴方がいなけりゃ 始まんない！
It won't start without you!
では、せーので 乾杯！
Now, one-two, Cheers!
おまけに 飲めない青くん 見たくない！
In addition, I don't want to see Ao-kun who can't drink!
この身果てるまで 命果てるまで
Until this body perishes, until life ends
火女（ひめ）の幸せに 尽くして頂戴！
Please devote yourself to the Princess's happiness!
飲んで！ 飲んで！ 飲んで！
Drink! Drink! Drink!
座右の銘は Drinking Knight!
The motto is Drinking Knight!
泡沫の向こう側に消えた本音と
The true feelings that disappeared beyond the bubbles
恍惚な表情のHoney Tonight Tonight Tonight...諸行無常
Honey with an ecstatic expression Tonight Tonight Tonight... all things are transient
僕を待ち受けるのは 裁きか救いか？
What awaits me, judgment or salvation?
考える必要はない
No need to think
「愛してるって言ってるじゃん…」
I'm telling you, I love you...
今宵、皆Party さあParty 踊り明かそう
Tonight, everyone's at a party, let's party, dance all night
ふらついてるHoneyからCalling
Calling from a staggering Honey
Tonight Tonight Tonight...自問自答
Tonight Tonight Tonight... self-questioning
この世は天国か？それとも地獄か？
Is this world heaven? Or hell?
正解などないんじゃない 音に乗っかって Come on!
There might be no right answer, get on the sound, Come on!
馬鹿になっていいじゃない？
It's okay to be a fool, isn't it?
僕らはまだ
We are still...
足りてないって、酔えてない
Not enough, not drunk enough
(Welcome to the "Blue Fire")
はい、ありがとうございました！
Yes, thank you very much!
どうでしたか？どうでしたか？どうでしたか？
How was it? How was it? How was it?
僕の初めてのオリジナル曲！
My very first original song!
なんとこの後、アニメーションMVが出るので
Actually, an animated MV will be released after this
サビのダンス一緒に踊ってね！
So please dance the chorus together with me!
めっちゃ気合入れたMVなんで絶対見てください！
The MV is really high effort, so please be sure to check it out!
ということで、
And so...
告知があります！
I have an announcement!
誕生日グッズが出るよ！ドン！
Birthday merchandise is coming out! Bam!
火威青 誕生目記念 2025
Hiodoshi Ao Birthday Anniversary 2025
1つ目はこちら！
First one is this!
キミの王子様☆青くんフレームアートボード
Your Prince Ao-kun Frame Art Board
キミの王子様 青くんフレームアートボード！
Your Prince Ao-kun Frame Art Board!
イラストはむっしゅママにお願いしています。
The illustration is by Mush-mama.
オリジナルアイドル衣装を着た僕がめっちゃかっこいいアートボードになっています。
It's a really cool art board featuring me in my original idol outfit.
印刷もこだわっているので、ぜひ見てください。
We've put a lot of care into the printing, so please check it out.
2つ目はこちら！
Second one is this!
青くんおしゃれランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー
Ao-kun Stylish Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keychain
青くんおしゃれランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー！
Ao-kun Stylish Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keychain!
イラストは万歳寿大宴会先生にお願いしています。
The illustrations are by Banzai Kotobuki Daienkai-sensei.
あの、よく「歌ってみた」とかで依頼してる推し神絵師ですね。
They're my favorite amazing artist who I often commission for "Utattemita" videos.
いろんなお洋服をね、依頼して、あの、いろんなもん、本当マジ最強のかっこいいのやってもらったんで。
I requested various outfits and they did a really, truly cool job.
はい、かっこいい！次！
Yes, cool! Next!
キミの王子様☆青くんぬいぐるみ
Your Prince Ao-kun Plushie
キミの王子様 青くんぬいぐるみ！
Your Prince Ao-kun Plushie!
衣装原案は先ほどのアートボード、むっしゅママにお願いしています。
The costume design is by Mush-mama, who did the art board earlier.
ぬいぐるみデザイン原案は今回も僕がやりました。
And I did the plushie design draft again this time.
なんかめっちゃ今時っぽいぬいぐるみにめっちゃなってるんで、
It's turned into a really modern-style plushie,
ぜひデートに連れて行ってください。
So please take it with you on dates.
はい、次はこちら！
Alright, next is this!
青くんのシャンパングラス
Ao-kun's Champagne Glass
青くんのシャンパングラス！
Ao-kun's Champagne Glass!
僕と言ったらやっぱりシャンパングラスだよね。
When you think of me, it's gotta be a champagne glass, right?
僕にシャンパンを入れるつもりでぜひ手に入れてください。
Please get it and imagine you're pouring champagne for me.
最後はこちら！
Finally, this one!
ASMRボイス 「ライブ終わりにキミと2人きりで」
ASMR Voice "Just the Two of Us After the Live"
ASMRボイス「ライブ終わりにキミと2人きりで」。
ASMR Voice "Just the Two of Us After the Live".
このボイスは今日このライブが終わった後にキミと2人で、お家デートをする、そんな内容になっています。
This voice content is about an at-home date with you after this live performance ends today.
いつも...
Always...
続いて！
Next!
フルセット購入特典はこちら！
Here are the full set purchase bonuses!
通常バージョンでは、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードが特典に付いてきます。
The standard version includes a foil-stamped replicated sign cheki-style bromide card as a bonus.
数量限定バージョンでは、直筆サインをこう、書くので、よろしくお願いします！
For the limited quantity version, I'll be writing hand-signed autographs, so please look forward to it!
また、フルセット共通特典として、青くんからのメッセージボイスもあります！
Also, as a common bonus for all full sets, there's a message voice from Ao-kun!
これは完全にアドリブで撮ったものなので、その時の気持ちを受け取ってね。
This was recorded completely ad-libbed, so please receive my feelings from that moment.
はい、ということで。
Yes, so...
そして、タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、ホロライブタレントカードです！
And as a full set bonus for the Talent Premium Goods, it's a Hololive Talent Card!
えー、去年から発売されたホロライブ公式カードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付きます。
Uh, it comes with one card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game released last year.
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となります。
The card is only available to those who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典に付くのは推しをアピールできるキーカード「推しホロメンカード」です。
The bonus is a 'Oshi Holomen Card', a key card to appeal your oshi.
カードの詳細や遊び方については、ホームページにてご確認ください！
Please check the website for card details and how to play!
ということで、グッズ紹介はこんな感じ！
So, that's it for the goods introduction!
はぁ...このあとすぐ、
Phew... right after this,
オリ曲のMV公開があります！
the MV for my original song will be released!
メン限のアンコールライブにも、ぜひ遊びに来てね！
Be sure to come visit the encore live for members too!
ということで、僕の3Dライブに
So, for coming to my 3D live,
来てくれて本当にありがとうー！
thank you so much!
愛・し・て・る・よー！！
I. Love. You!!
バイバイー！
Bye bye!
MV絶対見てねー！
Be sure to watch the MV!
あてっ、あてっ...
Ouch, ouch...
バイバイー！
Bye bye!
最高のバースデーをありがとう！
Thank you for the best birthday!
愛してるよ〜〜♡
I love you~~♡
愛してるって言ってるじゃん。
I told you I love you, didn't I?
今宵、君とParty さあ Party 踊り明かそう
Tonight, with you, Party, come on, Party, let's dance the night away
フラついているHoney さあ Darling
Staggering Honey, come on, Darling
Tonight Tonight Tonight もう一度
Tonight Tonight Tonight, once more
この世は天国か？それとも地獄さ
Is this world heaven? Or is it hell?
正解などない じゃない 音に乗っかって Come on!
There's no such thing as a correct answer, right? Ride the sound, Come on!